I think an llm combined with tools and
combined with agents they give you
massively better results so I I made a
little thing that watches me on the
camera and when I ate this instead of
typing it was listening to me in voice
mode and so now I can switch between two
modes and I'm just sitting on the
sofa you're listening to the AI native
Dev brought to you by Tesla
[Music]
[Applause]
on today's episode joining us once again
is Mr Patrick D the father of devops but
this time around we're not going to be
talking about devops Patrick it's GNA be
a nice refreshing change for you right
we're going to be talking about the
journey that you had using coding
assistance learning to develop using AI
as part of your workflow I've been
watching from AAR sometimes quite close
seeing how you've been playing around
with various these editors tooling
assistance it's been really fun to watch
the passion that you have in AI in
general but also how it can actually
help you build software so let's jump
straight in Patrick father of devops and
many other accolades but today Koda
Patrick tell us a little bit about your
background first of all briefly in the
when don't we do the coding space
because I think everyone knows you from
the devop space coding Patrick what does
that look like there's definitely a link
between devops doing a lot of automation
but particularly excited about how we
can now automate more of our code
generation and I see it also a way to
standardize the way we work make it more
consistent make it more secure there's
loads of opportunities that machines are
tireless helping us to do this where in
the past part of my job was VP
engineering scaling this out to all the
engineers the best practices now I have
a that can help developers to do this
all day and kind of get better for the
good cause yeah so yeah yeah awesome so
let's go back to the early stages of the
first time trying out a as part of your
coding style what did you use was it
co-pilot was it earlier than co-pilot I
think at that time chat gbd came out the
first plugins were actually more like
chat GPT pilot so they were like vs
codes I know there was GI up co-pilot
but at the time I was maybe not doing
too much of the coding but there was a
difference between doing it in line in
your editor by commenting and making
sure it was generating or autocompletion
thing and the next thing that came about
a little bit with chat gbt was the fact
that we could ask it questions and to do
things so that kind of chat pain on the
side helped to do things we've come a
long way initially it was like okay
here's a block of code and it rarely ran
now it's a lot more refined on
immediately getting the code into your
edit edor and doing there but there kind
of was the switch the inline editing was
not always working too well at that time
but I'm talking like early a couple of
years ago in mind editing being changing
existing code or no more like you write
a comment and then it auto completes to
the comment right and then the auto
completion was a little bit better but
we we c a completion before so that was
helpful but not good enough at that time
now it's tremendously better but that
was for me it's nice but it sometimes
gets in my way and then the chat came
and that was nice but it also felt like
why am I copy and pasting this all the
time you felt like going out to stack
Overflow coming back it was not exactly
what you needed but it was a new way a
second way that we're interacting with
llms or AI models to generate code that
we would do and generate in our code
basis as well it strikes me here and
thinking back to a blog post actually
that Geo wrote which mentioned on the
monthly a few weeks back he wrote about
this Matrix of change is trust and it's
really interesting to see here and we
see this with a number of tools whereby
various tools let's take chat GPT in
fact let's take something like clawed
with artifacts as a great example you
can you use it as an interface to ask
questions to write to make changes to
code and that's fine so long as you
don't want to change code and the change
piece there the the the change in
workflow is massive we're no longer an
ID we're not writing code so the way in
which we're interacting is a very big
change but then there are other tools
like cursor then allow for that
conversational aspect what is it what
what do they call it in cursor it's
compos composer that's the composer and
it allows you to say I want to change
this or I want that multifile change
whatever it is but it pushes it straight
back into the IDE so from the change
perspective while it's considered an an
advancement because it reduces the copy
pasting that we need to do it pushes us
back into more the existing workflow
rather than potentially what could be
the the the the later down the road
workflow yeah do you think we see
adoption for for various tools maybe
like more like the cursors and things
like that because they're just far
closer to where we are comfortable
working and is that going to almost like
Trump various other tools like uh like
whether it's from or or chat GPT and
things like that interestingly enough
the chat interface when the chat GPT
plugins came they already had things
like oh can you refactor this code can
you explain me this code all those kind
of functionality came extra but they
fell on the site and as you say now we
can do this like with our code base and
it's writing these things in the code
base I think whether you using codium or
Codi or like a lot of people have looked
at it like this way of doing this
together I think what cursor cracked was
ux problem of us expressing what we
wanted the intent we wanted changing
that code that's something we could have
done with copy and paste but they
streamline the process they optimize the
process and then the next part they did
is when we're reviewing all the edited
code a brilliant thing they did is
they're not just showing us the diff
they're not just showing us the inline
thing they're showing us a condensed
version of what is changing so they're
helping us to validate the code that has
been changing and I think that's the
biggest nice aspect that hey it brought
us into the flow hey we're writing and
we're expressing is it good and then we
reviewing so all these kind of things
got Polished in the workflow and I saw
that and I think it was a LinkedIn tweet
sorry a LinkedIn tweet LinkedIn post a
LinkedIn post a LinkedIn face insta post
that you did yeah where it was basically
three things you had the discussion the
diff so literally like a git diff right
what was removed what was added and then
a Shand these are the things that it's
describing it's done so effectively
almost like a code review on what it's
done in case there are big changes so
it's the ux that kind of crack that and
was that one of the big problems when
you were looking at whether it's
co-pilot or something in the early days
what was the killer feature I guess you
were missing in those early days to to
move to the next step and what was that
next step if you're coding and you're
somehow in the flow right you you want
it to be Snappy right so you want it to
be hey I need the information when I
want it I want to review and the first
time that cycle with cursor felt like oh
this is it it keeps me into the flow the
other things were like okay now I go
somewhere on the side and know in the
past it might have been a stack Overflow
then it was a chat but now everything
came into this is the problem I focus on
this is the next thing I need to think
about give me the result oh this is the
next thing you need to think about and
kind of that amazing flow started to
happen it doesn't mean that the answers
were perfect y but then the brilliant
thing was if you doing code completion
you get one completion and you're like H
it's not what I wanted and you're like
okay Escape because it's not what you
want brought multiple line completions
and multi completions as well so they
brought that into steroids but then when
you use compose you just say I want a
file that does it like this and prints
out that and it it gives you an answer
and when you're not happy with the
answer you just say change this yeah and
then you see so you're having that
conversational aspect not on the chat
but immediately with your code and with
a whole code base so not just the one
file it understands everything of your
code base so it was aligning multiple
things that were there before in a kind
of streamlined process that me as a
developer I found myself more and more
just not typing the code but just
nudging the llm or the tool to say this
is what I want no a little bit more like
that oh that's good that's not good so
that reviewing process got like insanely
different so let's talk about that in
terms of an accuracy point it's funny
when you talk a lot of people who are
still a little bit skeptical about AI
coding or just not want like trying to
push it off a little bit too much very
often you hear different levels of
Acceptance in terms of the how accurate
the suggestions are whether it's what
they want whether it's even the style of
implementation that they want maybe they
want to do it in a different way is it
something that you care about enough in
terms of the way it something's been
implemented do you care about it like I
wanted to use this type of set or
collection or whatever versus this one
do you care about that anymore or is it
more the functionality that you want it
to achieve that you're actually mostly
discussing with the chat it's a dilemma
do we still care about the code how it
looks like or you know do we just care
is it your code anymore or is it your
description of what the code should do I
think my argument would be is that I
still care in a way that when it fails
as a human I still won't understand how
it works and why it works yeah and
navigating my code base could not just
be a bunch of files naming A.P and b.p
so there is a cognitive piece that I
want to still understand what it is what
I see myself more and more do is I have
a specific problem that I want to solve
I start off almost with a blank kind of
project and I iterate on that using
cursor and compose so it's it's like a
very well- defined thing and then I
bring this into my bigger project and
then in that bigger project I have more
rules specified on how I want things so
one of of the cool things of course is
besides taking the whole code base
having to compos was that you describe a
little bit of a rules that the
generations should adhar to like I'm
coding in react and my front end I
always want to have an API test written
in open API spec I want all those things
so more and more I could write my set of
rules like they call it cursor rules and
cursor well generating takes that into
as not just the context of your code
base but it also takes that like your
guidelines that he wants to take to
generate the code that kind of sometimes
gets into the way for smaller project
yeah but for bigger project that's how
you make it consistent across the whole
code base yeah and I presume even with
the smaller projects there will be basic
things that you will want to inherit
from General development and so we'll
start with that so in terms of how we
provide this type of context there'll
probably be some various system prompts
that we'll always want to use adding
these are you creating these as like
files like supporting files that you
include and reference in the composer or
is there another way you include them
because you obviously you don't want to
provide too much context or overwhelm it
with huge number of instructions so you
want to be almost a little bit surgical
in saying I'm working on the back end
here I want you to use these backend
requirements essentially yeah when
you're creating these suggestions so I
have a base set of requirements I put in
my project that I reuse across projects
and then while doing specific stuff I
add specific files let's say I'm doing
front end stuff yeah then I'm
specifically saying add front end specs
to this so that kind of is a a balance
between what I'm trying to achieve in
the code and it's the same thing with
adding documentation depending on what I
want to bring in is something that I
decide on the moment yeah so if you're
specifying too much it sometimes gets
upset or it has conflicts and the
codee's not always that good so I I do
trig this in in small bits when I'm
asking it to generate the code while I'm
doing this and if you didn't add that
kind of like context or like reference
these various files presumably you would
still get to the same end point but you
would then have to iterate on its
response more more into the prompt yeah
so you have more of a discussion going
going forward so actually it's not quite
how I would like to do that I want to do
it like this it's interesting there was
a good quote from Dez trainer actually
he said something along the lines of the
our willingness or our ability to want
to write short prompts is robbing us
from the need to be able to you know
provide it with the detail it needs in
order to give me the right answer and it
feels like this is effectively doing
both it provides us with the longer
prompt the information it needs to say
this is what I want you this is how I
want you to provide me the good answers
but we're still being able to short
prompt it we're still being able to say
look I want this we don't have to say
exactly the detail of how we want so
you're almost like adding that little
bit of background knowledge into the
responses but it's like humans when I
say do a certain thing and we have a lot
of history and a lot of context already
with two words yeah and so if I bring in
a lot of context in my editor and I
provide it with a set of rules it can
infer from the things that I want more
information a lot of the tools have like
prompt compilers they convert your
simple prompt to more complex prompt to
get better results so this is definitely
one of the ways they're getting but the
only way they do this if you give them
more context or specificity getting that
detail out of your actually out of your
mind yeah yeah interesting another tool
that you used was ader right you use
that before cursor or yeah that was
before cursor precs a precursor so AER
is one of those open- Source tools to
generate code it's a little bit
different from other tools in that it is
more CLI based so their approach was you
coding but at the same time you're
running it like a demon in your CLI and
you give it what you want similar to a
chat and he changed the code I think the
quality was really good at what it was
generating but there were a few quotes
that worked against me one is it was
autoc committing code that he thought
was good which color of course you could
disable it but it was like one of those
things do we really want this they had
some cool things like I can talk with
voice to it oh nice and so I I can have
that iteration look more on a verbal
thing which is also something I tried
with cursor to make it like talk and
have that conversation because I I can
just sit on the bench and talk to it why
am we still typing and it's almost like
that peer programming thing as well
right we actually when a lot of the time
when you just that there at a keyboard
sometimes you skip through various
checks in your mind whereas actually
when you're trying to say something
you're thinking it through more and and
so as a result you you I guess you you
like find tun exactly what you're asking
for which is interesting but Adar has
what's nice is they blog a lot about how
they do things so they talk about how
they do their internal diffing and
sending small chunks uh to D llm so it's
not overloaded with the whole code base
so that they kind of work from there
this is also something cursor does is
they almost prioritize which part of the
context are useful to solve your part of
your problems so which is like
optimizing for Speed and context because
if you give them too much it's just a
problem yeah something I recently added
is when the code is being generated they
have the notion of an architect
reviewing your code it's just the llm
taking another identity but it critiques
your code as being generated so you
don't have to do it yourself but
obviously latency plays into a big uh
thing there because you want your code
quick and you don't want to wait like
for a minute so there's a lot of caching
optimization of the tools happening but
they're they're very open about it and
it's pretty cool you can learn a lot
about the source and you know how good
would you say those types of tools are a
truly understanding code and do you feel
I see a lot of tools either mixing AI so
LM versus a symbolic AI or something
like that or using static analysis of
codes to better understand and model the
architecture or the as of your code yeah
what's your experience been in those
various approaches in truly providing
good feedback versus just a very general
feedback which can be hit and miss it's
one of those conceptions that people
they look at chat chip they ask it to
generate something and they don't like
what they see and they dismiss the whole
option I think an llm combined with
tools and combined with agents they give
you massively better results but what
could go into some of the tools you
mentioned that when it's cutting up your
code you don't want it to be cut in the
middle of a sentence or a line of your
code it needs to understand your code
that's why people are using a uh so the
syntax tree abstract syntax tree to
parse things and chunk it up to the
right pieces so that's one layer of of
kind of improving which I was guessing
when you were like talking about about
when it when the tools use various parts
of the project or the code AS context
because it knows those are relevant
pieces I was wondering if it was using
something like an a to work that out
whether most of them are doing this to
correctly divide the pieces in the right
pieces they need to look up or they need
to change so that's one thing then
imagine the the codes being generated
what you want in like a code generation
pipeline you wanted to somehow specify
and generate the test
that it's doing one of the tests could
be like I take the prompt and I convert
it somehow into a functional test some
of I forgot the name but some of the
code editors actually are doing this
first they right to test first and they
help you write the tests and then they
have the llm write the code because then
you have your test harness and they have
a better chance of success because the
whole thing about TD was actually
refining what you wanted and how you
wanted to see it and then they give
better hints to the so that's another
thing there's loads of other tools you
can lint things when it's generated is
it valid syntax that's an easy one so
you can feed that back hey there was an
error or that you can run the code if
it's a piece but then you need
sandboxing there's all kind of security
issues can I run this but in a pipeline
some of those parts you could do and you
can see whether it executes and does not
have like issues or it actually runs the
tests as also an execute and give that
back there's other things people have
been putting in there that there's so
many tools that we use in our head but
these llms could use another one is code
smells yeah so if I'm editing the code
and my code smells increase I do not
want to have that code so they feed this
back again people from code scene they
do a lot of stuff kind of detecting
because a lot of the refactoring is you
do not want your code smells to go up
and so feeding this back into the loop
he it's not okay so I'll generate
another and that's under the hood it's
not like the end user see it but
obviously the longer the pipeline gets
the longer the latency again but if you
look at coding agents that just run and
run so not specifically in your code
editor they could do this all day right
so they can just run and see if it's
optimized and and go from there there's
other pieces of optimization that you
have maybe you f tune your model based
on the code based on your guidelines
deliberately in
errors and see if they're caught and
they're not good so there's like a whole
thing that people are doing this and the
other thing that people have learn is
when they do changes is they do smaller
changes and not like the big chunk with
all the context but it's almost like the
humans they need to understand almost
like the your code editor view plus and
minus one yeah and that's the context
they give it and then they stuff a lot
of conexs around it but people are
coming back from stuffing all the code
into the LM and see what happens too
much context basically overloading it
with context let's talk about what you
did with curx I think that was super
interesting Beyond going Beyond cursor
you made a couple of updates yourself
built up on cursor tell us a little bit
about some of the adjustments you made
first of all what was the problem that
caused you to do this and and then how
did you do that the first one is so
having looked a lot at the pipelines and
did my fair share of trying to make it
work sometimes you just want to use it
right and as cursor was one of the
better ones and like helped it really
give good results I thought it will be
really nice to use that kind of whole
logic inside of my own project but
cursor is an IDE it's not supposed to do
any editing and so on so what I did is I
wrote a combination of a vs Cod plugin
that allows you to type and an open CV
project that looks at your screen and
see whether cursor is open and then
grabs the text and so on So eventually
was able to wrap the ID to an API so I
could just say run this give me the CH
that you generated and go from there and
my whole idea was that I can now compare
cursor with copilot with all the stuff
and I I just use the best tool but most
of the tools were closed in a way that
they're in the ID and you can't do
anything about so that was why I I
wanted to do this and then I could drive
this code generation and add this as a
tool to my agent yeah so I I got the
best of all bre so I guess there's a
couple of next steps on that the first
one is you could effectively automate it
to say look this is what I want you five
tools go and do it in the way you want
to do it provide me with the results I
can then choose which result I want to
use and so you're effec if you're
running a team of developers that are
playing off each other and you can say
actually this is the one I want and
these are the reasons why I don't want
the others that's one way a second way
could be to automate that and then say
is there a way I could actually take a
tool that actually reviews that code and
identifies the best of the options and
suggests the best option to me and to
why this was the best option around
other codes there's like levels of you
effectively being almost like a team
lead of these AI developer agents yeah
and you're managing that team
effectively yeah indeed and then you
have the reviewing agent the code
writing agent and yeah so that was my
motivation to play and and make that
into an API but how successful was that
in terms of then being able to get
results back that you would be more
likely to accept it it it wasn't about
being more likely to accept but it was
more like I can use it for my own tools
right so that was the usefulness now I
didn't have to write the whole pipeline
somebody wrote it for me and I can just
use it consume that dat or however you
want in your next step yeah and the
second tool was about we mentioned this
already before I found myself reviewing
code more and then commenting on the
code and I first tried I think a voice
recording assistive tool because then I
wouldn't have to type anymore right so I
was like okay but I found that even vs
code has a voice assistant it is only
typing into the code editor it was not
typing into the cursor editor yes or
kind of all the fields then I went to an
accessibility tool with the voice but
then I figured I was doing this and my
wife came in and started talking to me
all of a sudden I got like things on my
screen I do this and sometimes I still
needed that keyboard for the shortcut
for Activation yeah and I didn't want to
do that I actually came across an AIT
tool called cursor L there's no kind of
connect between both but they had a
fascinating view about using sounds like
to activate certain things and then they
would say little red putter which means
click on the next word with a red p in
the editor so they annotate the whole
edit a little bit like what three words
for it's very complex so I figured like
how can I do this and what I ultimately
ended up with was I thought when you
want to have somebody listen to you what
do you do you raise your finger yeah
right okay so I made a little thing that
watch just me on the camera and when I
read this instead of typing it was
listening to me in voice mode yeah but
then there's a difference between like
when I say do this command is it now
typing or do I want it to execute yeah
so I basically switch between this is
typing and this is executing a command
yeah and so now I can switch between two
modes and I'm just sitting on the sofa
saying like you know okay you know this
is the two fingers compos activate yeah
it brings up composer yeah then I say
I'm typing what I want and then I say
okay so I'm just switching with my
fingers and if you turn the fingers
around you get very angry at the idea if
you choose absolutely anyway I'm a big
fan of the open AI real time interaction
a lot of people think of it as clunky
but it is able to talk conversationally
back to you in a very good way and the
other thing they solved was I can
interrupt the speech so it's not okay
damn now it's reading off my whole diff
yeah yeah yeah right so it's like that's
that's not what I want yeah so I had
some shortcuts by saying open compose
and he was listening for the words open
compose and kind of activating it on
that but then I went a step further and
I thought but the llm is can just look
at my text yeah and I hooked it up with
function calling and so if he thinks it
should trigger the function open compose
however I say it orever it determines it
it's going to bring up open composer so
now I don't have to specifically say
anymore okay this function is with that
trigger word if you don't know the
trigger word it's just listening on the
conversation and I just can keep adding
more tools yeah oh now I'm going into my
browser and when I go into my browser
you probably want to take a screenshot
and you want to upload it into my cursor
because then you can look and generate
me the front end
yeah that I wanted so this is just a
conversational way that I I brought up
that's brilliant I love it and I would
love to almost see if there was a
whiteboard behind us for example and
we're drawing out some architecture and
it can start recognizing the
architecture and and almost using that
as a format that we can describe and get
code written in certain places there's a
ton of things where it can take more
than just the the text input and
actually take visual cues like you just
mentioned as well like you would ask
what's on my screen yeah and it would
tell you what's on your screen kind of
like how do I improve it okay just
suggestions now recently certainly at
the time of recording this but maybe a
few weeks ago when for people who are
listening there was some recent
additions to B Claude whereby there is a
beta that has been released or beta for
our us friends they effectively have
some screen scraping technology that can
identify what's in your screen and even
interact so you're effectively having a
coder who can write into your ID
whatever it is even if there's no
support for AI and things like that in
that ID because anthropic is now looking
at your screen how do you feel about
that kind of thing first of all I think
it makes sense when I would use chat GPT
and I'm in a store what do I do I take a
picture and like okay what do I need to
know and and we've been in the IDE using
this on the OS it's very simple similar
to what I say what's on my screen how
can you improve this so now it's the
next step what they did is it's allowed
to execute something locally yeah but it
it is just another tool but now they run
this locally I think this was an
evolution also Microsoft has a way that
they record everything that ever went on
your screen and you're able to recall
remember that spreadsheet Simon that we
worked on last Friday or something boom
Oh my God oh my God you didn't you
didn't see that spreadsheet yeah yeah no
so that kind of is in eminent in a way
that the tools are just getting more on
the local IDE and one of the the things
like with my toing I had to determine if
it's what's on my screen as well because
is it now cursor or was it my browser so
the machines were looking at the context
I was able to do this by looking at the
process list and which was one was on my
screen but you could definitely look at
other ways the other thing I I had to do
was I had to look where a certain dial
was and you could train a model say look
at the screen where's a certain dial but
then tomorrow there's something else and
then if you would have an if statement
list of saying if a dial then that it
will not be very efficient but if I
would train a model that just
understands all the software tooling
we're using today and and recognizes
what kind of screen what are the actions
you're supposed to be taking when you
this in front of your screen yeah I know
people are trying to make this even more
self-learning is they look at again it's
hooking it up with a tool they look at
it from the accessibility inspector like
they look at the buttons on the screen
and then they look like are they
clickable can we do something with that
then they look at the hints of the
screen what they can do so this has been
a little bit going on in a research
project called OS world where they're
already doing this in a virtual machine
and you can spin this up and it gives
you a desktop and then they try all out
out all these scenarios open my screen
open my browser do this and it's very
similar to what I've described like
hooking up for with the function calling
once you know what's there then you can
take the next step on kind of those
things yeah would I trust it security
security was the next kind of thing cuz
it once it basically has access to
whatever is on your screen you don't
know what's going to pop up on your
screen next and and how do you control
what it should and shouldn't have access
to and I think there's a wider problem
here and around authorization and things
like that and we've talked with people
toor yosu gave some really interesting
thoughts about how glean actually have
their authorization as a step before the
llm working out what its users actually
do have access to and then providing the
llm with what's the user should access
versus have the LM try and work that out
and understand that because you have to
assume the LM is like a user in that
respect you don't have that control
necessarily when you allow someone to
completely look at your screen so does
that worry you at all from the security
point of view personal data anything
like that I think it does in a way that
I would run this on a virtual desktop
yeah and be sure what I give access to
it and not obviously not everybody was
supposed to be tax savy at a certain
point you understand what is allowed and
what is allowed not allowed I think
there is an inherent problem with the
llm in that there is hallucination yes
we're trying to reduce it but we are
never sure what it's going to do so we
might restrict what it's able to do
that's our best thing but then obviously
if you wanted to change document files
will you stop and then you get a thest
thing like when it's going to ask you
every time can I change this Doc and
you're just GNA say okay yeah whatever
so that compliance is worrisome in a way
that we know the technology inherently
is not always of repeatable that it's
always giving the same result but it's
incredible to be able to share context
across applications that's going to be
so powerful I think and the intent as
well to be able to say I'm in this app
this is the level that the user requires
this detail on but now I'm in an IDE I
need to create actual implementation and
go much much lower level to to provide
value amazing before we close I'd love
to talk a little bit of more breth in
terms of when you are coding what other
assistant tools have you played with
that has really added value most value
to your coding experience thinking here
whether it's test support whether it's
documentation support whether it's
anything else like that the one that I
quite often use is Fe zero which is from
for a front end generation yeah yeah so
that helps you and I think it's nice
that you specify the website that you
want they generated code and you can
iterate on that and now you can SN this
back in to your redo as well so it's an
additional tool the cursors and the like
are not really focused on that but it
helps you with the front end kind of
stuff I've been exploring a tool called
runme dodev which is more of a tool on
writing notebooks for devops commands
another way of not they writing all the
scripts but keeping mixture of
documentation in there the documentation
I usually do in line like one of my
specification is like whenever you write
something add documentation so there's a
lot more tool around that and the other
tool is now I have to think it was e2b
if I'm not mistaken for sandboxing I
always mess the letters up so those
three but for sandbox execution of
functions so I I get like a fast
execution solution all a little bit
similar to a kind of like a repet style
would you say or different the rep it is
similar but this one is very focused on
sandboxing and execution got um so it's
easy to integrate your code yeah if you
want something to happen yeah and the
other tool gosh I use all the tools and
don't remember the name but I think the
other one was AI inspect and allows you
to do much like evaluations but in your
vs code it's like a somewhere government
project but what's really nice and most
of the evaluations they take a long time
they run somewhere else like as Lang
Smith and and so on but this plugin
allows me to keep it into the vs code
yeah uh and have the runs also AC cross
multiple llms and see which one was the
best for this kind of aspect so those
are a few add-ons to the tool amazing
and for people who are just thinking
about starting off and wanting to try
something what kind of of all the tools
that you've mentioned is cursor the one
that you would start off with or
something else I guess if you're very
much into front end you go to the vzero
yeah if you're a little bit more into
the generate whole applications there's
another one called bolt. new and then
cursor if your day-to-day Cod riding
back end front end yeah that's the one I
I put to and then there's the obvious
ones like anthropic artifacts that help
you as well for generating some of the
stuff so those are a typical tool base
but I think what's happening is that all
the tools they're learning from each
other yeah and hopefully you have
everything somewhere Clos into one tool
which is interesting for example one of
the next gith up co-pilots they will
look at your test coverage and then they
suggest tests also something you can use
everybody's exploring and maybe that was
another reason why to build an API
around it because then I can use
whatever tool for the right job and uh
amazing Patrick it's been a blast as
always to have a chat and thank you for
so much like very practical Hands-On
tips and and tooling suggestions for
people so no no excuses now go out and
have a play and and see what you think
let us know what you're using what
you're enjoying thanks again Patrick for
joining us uh twice the first person
twice on
on the native my pleasure in a couple of
months we'll automate it ourselves doing
the podcast like notebook llm yeah there
we go there we go we can just relax on a
beach somewhere watching our own jobs
being done better than we can B amazing
thanks very much and join see you on the
next
[Music]
[Applause]
episode thanks for tuning in join us
next time on the AI native Dev brought
to you by Tesla
[Music]